Finding aid to Buildings records CA.MS.00104
Smith College Archives
- Libraries
  - -William Allan Neilson Library
    - -Pamphlets
      - -Usage Guides, 1957-1982 (Box 234, Folder 17)
    - -Plaques and Named Gifts, 1961- (Box 234, Folder 18)
    - -Policy
      - -General, 1910 (Box 234, Folder 19)
      - -Circulation, 1909- (Box 234, Folder 20)
      - -Emergency Manual, undated (Box 234, Folder 21)
      - -Hours, 1909-1987 (Box 234, Folder 22)
      - -Reserve Books, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 23)
    - -Rare Book Room (Mortimer Rare Book Room)
      - -General, 1963- (Box 234, Folder 24)
      - -Accessions, 1954-1975 (Box 234, Folder 25)
      - -Brochures and Pamphlets, 1985 (Box 234, Folder 26)
      - -Collections, 1979- (Box 234, Folder 27)
      - -Dedication, 1994 (Box 234, Folder 28)
      - -Exhibits and Events, 1954- (Box 234, Folder 29)
      - -Incunabula Lists, 1964; 1975 (Box 234, Folder 30)
      - -Publications, 1982-1987 (Box 234, Folder 31)
      - -Photographs, 1982-1983 (Box 234, Folder 32)
    - -Reading Period, 1940- (Box 234, Folder 33)
    - -Seelye Reading Room, 1940-1941 (Box 234, Folder 34)
    - -Vault, 1917- (Box 234, Folder 35)
    - -WPA Survey, 1941 (Box 234, Folder 36)
    - -Report on the Need for an Accession Record, 1939 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Sep 1939 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Oct-Nov 1939 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Dec 1939-Feb 1940 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, Mar-May 1940 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - -Accessions, 1947-1955 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - -Accessions, Jan 1956-Apr 1957 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - -Accessions, May-Dec 1969 (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jun 1970 (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Dec 1970 (Box 235.1, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, 1971 (Box 235.1, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Mar 1972 (Box 235.1, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Apr-Jul 1972 (Box 235.1, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Sep 1972 (Box 235.1, Folder 5)
    - -Accessions, Oct-Dec 1972 (Box 235.2, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Jan-May 1973 (Box 235.2, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Sep 1975-Jul 1976 (Box 235.2, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Aug-Nov 1976 (Box 235.2, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Apr 1977 (Box 235.2, Folder 5)
    - -Accessions, May-Jul 1977 (Box 235.3, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 235.3, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jul 1978 (Box 235.3, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Sep 1978-Apr 1979 (Box 235.3, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, May-Aug 1979 (Box 235.3, Folder 5)
    - -Accessions, Sep-Dec 1979 (Box 235.4, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jun 1980 (Box 235.4, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Dec 1980 (Box 235.4, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Dec 1981 (Box 235.4, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jun 1982 (Box 235.4, Folder 5)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Dec 1982 (Box 235.5, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 235.5, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Dec 1983 (Box 235.5, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jul 1984 (Box 235.5, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, Aug-Dec 1984 (Box 235.6, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Jun 1985 (Box 235.6, Folder 2)
    - -Accessions, Jul-Dec 1985 (Box 235.6, Folder 3)
    - -Accessions, Jan-May 1986 (Box 235.6, Folder 4)
    - -Accessions, Jun-Dec 1986 (Box 235.7, Folder 1)
    - -Accessions, Jan-Feb 1987 (Box 235.7, Folder 2)
    - -Photographs
      - -Exterior
        - -Front View, 1909-1920; undated (Box 236, Folder 1)
        - -Front View, 1921-1960; undated (Box 236, Folder 2)
        - -Front View, 1961-; undated (Box 236, Folder 3)
        - -Rear View, 1911- (Box 236, Folder 4)
        - -Rear View, undated (Box 236, Folder 5)
        - -Rear View With Fountain, undated (Box 236, Folder 6)
        - -Special Features, undated (Box 236, Folder 7)
        - -Wings
          - -North Wing-Front View, 1937- (Box 236, Folder 8)
          - -North Wing-Rear View, 1937- (Box 236, Folder 9)
          - -North Wing-Construction, 1937 (Box 236, Folder 10)
          - -Northeast Wing, 1979- (Box 236, Folder 11)
          - -Northwest Wing, 1962 (Box 236, Folder 12)
          - -Northwest Wing-Construction, 1962 (Box 236, Folder 13)
          - -Northwest and South Wings-Architect's Photographs, 1961 (Box 236, Folder 14)
          - -South Wing, 1962- (Box 236, Folder 15)
          - -WANL/Alumnae Gym Complex, 1974- (Box 236, Folder 16)
        - -With Other Buildings, undated (Box 236, Folder 17)
      - -Interior
        [see Box 75]
      - -Groups and Individuals, 1960 (Box 236, Folder 18)
      - -Special Events (Box 236)
        - -75th Anniversary ('Birthday') Party, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 19)
        - -Dedication of Steps Inscription, 1997 (Box 236, Folder 20)
        - -Morgan Gallery Dedication, 1999 (Box 236, Folder 21)
        - -South Wing Groundbreaking and Dedication Ceremonies, 1962 (Box 236, Folder 22)
      - -Miscellaneous, 1979- (Box 236, Folder 23)
      - -Miscellaneous-Sets, 1937- (Box 236, Folder 24)
      - -Interior
        - -Browsing Room, 1910- (Box 236.1, Folder 1)
        - -Burack Room
          [see Libraries-WANL-Photographs-Interior-Reserve Room]
        - -Carrels, 1939- (Box 236.1, Folder 2)
        - -Catalog, 1951- (Box 236.1, Folder 3)
        - -Catalogue Department, 1962; undated (Box 236.1, Folder 4)
        - -Caverno Room, undated (Box 236.1, Folder 5)
          [see also Libraries-WANL-Photographs-Interior-Philosophy Seminar Room]
        - -Circulation Desk, 1911- (Box 236.1, Folder 6)
        - -Construction, 1961 (Box 236.1, Folder 7)
        - -Cosntruction, 1982 (Box 236.1, Folder 8)
        - -English Seminar Room, 1911 (Box 236.1, Folder 9)
        - -Entrance, 1979 (Box 236.1, Folder 10)
        - -Graduate Lounge, undated (Box 236.1, Folder 11)
        - -Grind Room, 1926 (Box 236.1, Folder 12)
        - -Halls and Stairs, 1977 (Box 236.1, Folder 13)
        - -History Seminar Room, 1920-1960 (Box 236.1, Folder 14)
        - -Librarian's Office, undated (Box 236.1, Folder 15)
        - -Lyon Reading Room, 1913 (Box 236.1, Folder 16)
        - -Mair Room, 1971- (Box 236.1, Folder 17)
        - -Microfilm Area, 1975- (Box 236.1, Folder 18)
        - -Periodical Room, 1909- (Box 236.1, Folder 19)
        - -Philip Hale Room, 1949- (Box 236.1, Folder 20)
        - -Philosophy Seminar Room, 1937 (Box 236.1, Folder 21)
          [see also Libraries-WANL-Photographs-Interior-Caverno Room]
        - -Rare Book Room, 1952- (Box 236.1, Folder 22)
        - -Reference, 1982-; undated (Box 236.1, Folder 23)
        - -Reserve Room, 1982 (Box 236.1, Folder 24)
        - -Schrager Room, undated (Box 236.1, Folder 25)
        - -Seelye Reading Room, 1910- (Box 236.1, Folder 26)
        - -Stacks, 1910- (Box 236.1, Folder 27)
        - -Staff Room, 1962- (Box 236.1, Folder 28)
        - -Technical Services, 1975 (Box 236.1, Folder 29)
        - -Unidentified, undated (Box 236.1, Folder 30)
    - -Sketches and Drawings, 1938 (Box 236.1, Folder 31)
- Lilly Hall
  - -General, 1886-1956 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - -General-Hampshire County Journal Article, 1886 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - -Alfred Theodore Lilly, 1890-1975 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - -Lilly Pad Coffeehouse, 1967 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - -Mwangi Cultural Center, 1989 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - -Photographs
    - -Building on Site of Lilly, 1875 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - -Exterior
      - -North Views, undated (Box 237, Folder 7)
      - -South Views, 1893- 1960; undated (Box 237, Folder 8)
      - -Special Features, 1976; undated (Box 237, Folder 9)
      - -With Other Buildings, 1900 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - -Interior-Classrooms and Labs, 1890-1915; undated (Box 237, Folder 11)
      [see also 52. Science]
    - -Interior-Lilly Pad, 1967 (Box 237, Folder 12)
- Look House
- Lyman House
  [see Delta Sigma Invitation House]
- Lyman Plant House (Conservatory)
  - -General-Architectural Plans, 1897-; undated (Box 237, Folder 13)
    [see Flat File Drawer 8 (Appendix H)]
  - -History, 1914-1998 (Box 237, Folder 14)
  - -Exhibits-Bulb Show, 1918- (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - -Exhibits-Chrysanthemum Show, 1918- (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exhibits-Bulb Show, 1944-; undated (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - -Exhibits-Chysanthemum Show, 1930-; undated (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - -Exterior, 1895-1920 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - -Exterior, 1921- (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - -Interior, 1900- (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - -Interior, undated (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - -Special Features, 1988; undated (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - -Plant Collection as of July 31, 1998 (Box 238, Folder 11)
  - -Sketches and Drawings, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 12)
- Lyman Road Apartments, 1961-1998 (Box 238, Folder 13)
- Maltby House / Miss Maltby's
- Mandelle Annex
  [see Paradise Road, #61]
- Mandelle Quadrangle
  [see Quadrangle-Mandelle Quadrangle, see Comstock House, and see Wilder House]
- Martha Wilson House
  - -General, 1926- (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - -House Library
    [see Libraries-House-Martha Wilson]
  - -New Student Handbooks, 1961- (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs
    - -Albums
      [see Box 79]
    - -Exterior, 1925- (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - -Exterior, undated (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - -Interior, undated (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - -Groups, 1926- (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - -Special Features, undated (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - -Sketches, Models, and Drawings (Architectural and Artistic), undated (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - -Photograph Album, 1956-1957 (Box 239.2)
  - -Photograph Album, 1957-1958 (Box 239.2)
  - -Photograph Album, 1958-1959 (Box 239.2)
  - -Photograph Album, 1959-1960 (Box 239.2)
  - -Photograph Album, 1960-1961 (Box 239.2)
  - -Photograph Album, 1961-1962 (Box 239.2)
- Mary Ellen Chase House
  - -General, 1979- (Box 239.1, Folder 1)
  - -Photographs-Exterior, 1967- (Box 239.1, Folder 2)
  - -Photographs-Groups, 1977-; undated (Box 239.1, Folder 3)
- Mary Lois James Alumnae House and Tea Room
  [see Alumnae House (8 Bedford Terrace location)]
- McCallum House, Paradise Rd.
  [see Paradise Road, # 58]
- McCallum House, Prospect St.
  [see Prospect Street, # 10]
- McCallum House, West St.-site of Pierce Hall
  [see Pierce Hall]
- Memorial Hall
  [see Libraries-Clarke Library]
- Mendenhall Center
  [see Center for the Performing Arts]
- Morgan Hall, 1937- 1950 (Box 239.1, Folder 4)
- Morris House
  - -General, 1904-; undated (Box 239.1, Folder 5)
  - -Artifacts
  - -Faceboards
  - -New Students' Booklet, 1987- (Box 239.1, Folder 6)
  - -Register / Roster, 1922-1952 (Box 239.1, Folder 7)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1893- (Box 239.1, Folder 8)
    - -Interior, 1894- (Box 239.1, Folder 9)
    - -Faceboard, 1982-1983 (Box 239.1, Folder 10)
    - -Faceboard, 1983-1984 (Box 239.1, Folder 11)
    - -Faceboard, 1984-1985 (Box 239.1, Folder 12)
    - -Faceboard, 2001-2002
      [see Oversize Box 14]
    - -Groups, 1895-1969 (Box 240.1, Folder 1)
    - -Groups, 1970- (Box 240.1, Folder 2)
    - -Seniors, 1946 (Box 240.1, Folder 3)
    - -50th Anniversary, 1943 (Box 240.1, Folder 4)
- Morrow House
  - -General, 1926- (Box 240.1, Folder 5)
  - -New Students' Handbook, undated (Box 240.1, Folder 6)
  - -Photographs
    - -Exterior, 1925- (Box 240.1, Folder 7)
    - -Interior, undated (Box 240.1, Folder 8)
    - -Groups, 1926- (Box 240.1, Folder 9)
- Museum of Art
  - -General, 1931- (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - -General-Clippings, 1879- (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - -Acquisitions, 1875-1939 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - -Acquisitions, 1940-1965 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - -Acquisitions, 1966- (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - -Acquisitions, undated (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - -Acquisitions-Gifts, 1925-; undated (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - -Acquisitions-Gifts-Procedures, 1966-; undated (Box 241, Folder 8)
  - -Annual Reports, 1947- (Box 241, Folder 9)
  - -Artists
    - -General, 1920-1965 (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - -Correspondence, 1910-1938 (Box 241, Folder 11)
    - -Exhibitors at Smith, 1962- (Box 241, Folder 12)
    - -Individuals
      - -Albers, Josef, 1964 (Box 241, Folder 13)
      - -Brush, George de Forest, 1918 (Box 241, Folder 14)
      - -Church, Frederick, 1900 (Box 241, Folder 15)
      - -Colman, Samuel, 1882 (Box 241, Folder 16)
      - -Constable, John, 1978 (Box 241, Folder 17)
      - -Craven, Thomas, 1931 (Box 241, Folder 18)
      - -de Kooning, Willem, 1965 (Box 241, Folder 19)
      - -Elmer, Edwin Romanzo, 1964-1978 (Box 241, Folder 20)
        [see also Flat File Drawer 9 (Appendix H)]
      - -French, Daniel Chester, 1920; 1974 (Box 241, Folder 21)
      - -Fry, Roger Eliot, 1932 (Box 241, Folder 22)
      - -Manship, Paul, 1914-1916 (Box 241, Folder 23)
      - -Motherwell, Robert, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 24)
      - -O'Keefe, Georgia, 1997 (Box 241, Folder 25)
      - -Picasso, Pablo, 1968- (Box 241, Folder 26)
      - -Rouault, Georges, 1936 (Box 241, Folder 27)
      - -Sheeler, Charles, 1940 (Box 241, Folder 28)
      - -Tamayo, Rufino, 1979- (Box 241, Folder 29)
      - -Thayer, Abbott Henderson, 1916- (Box 241, Folder 30)
      - -Usher, Leila, 1930 (Box 241, Folder 31)
      - -Whistler, James Abbott McNeill, 1879- (Box 241, Folder 32)
  - -Auctions, 1966- (Box 241, Folder 33)
  - -Catalogs and Lists, 1896-1932 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - -Catalogs and Lists, 1933- (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - -College Hall Art Gallery, 1880-1994 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - -Exhibits
    [see Boxes 87-94; see also Purchase Exhibitions; see also Appendix B for item-level list of oversize exhibit posters]
  - -Fine Arts Center (pre-1970) [FAC-]
    - -General-Renovations, 1932 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - -General-Renovations-Physical Plant Report, 1962 (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - -General-Photographs-Exterior, undated (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - -Graham Hall, 1907-1970 (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - -Graham Hall-Photographs-Exterior, 1897-1970 (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - -Graham Hall-Photographs-Interior, undated (Box 242, Folder 9)
    - -Hillyer Hall
      [see also Libraries-Hillyer Art Library]
      - -General, 1883-1970 (Box 242, Folder 10)
      - -Architectural Plans
        [see Flat File Drawers 8 and 9 (Appendix H)]
      - -Clippings, 1882-1977 (Box 242, Folder 11)
      - -Flood-see Museum of Art-Flood in Hillyer (Box 242)
      - -Hillyer Family, 1880 (Box 242, Folder 12)
      - -Photographs
        - -Exterior, 1882-1887 (Box 242, Folder 13)
        - -Exterior, 1888-1900 (Box 242, Folder 14)
        - -Exterior, 1901-1970 (Box 243, Folder 1)
        - -Exterior, undated (Box 243, Folder 2)
        - -Interior
          - -Gallery, 1910-1915 (Box 243, Folder 3)
          - -Gallery (Box 243)
          - -Life Room, 1900 (Box 243, Folder 4)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Alcove, 1890-1904 (Box 243, Folder 5)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Classes, 1904 (Box 243, Folder 6)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Pieta, 1884 (Box 243, Folder 7)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Romulus, etca., 1884 (Box 243, Folder 8)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Three Graces, 1904 (Box 243, Folder 9)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Three Graces, 1885 (Box 243, Folder 10)
          - -Sculpture Gallery-Miscellaneous, 1884 (Box 243, Folder 11)
          - -Studio, 1968 (Box 243, Folder 12)
          - -Studio Gallery, undated (Box 243, Folder 13)
        - -Demolition, 1970 (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - -Tryon Hall
      - -General, 1923-1970 (Box 243, Folder 15)
      - -Architectural Plans
      - -Sculpture Garden, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 16)
      - -Photographs
        - -Exterior, 1923-1970 (Box 243, Folder 17)
        - -Exterior-Sculpture Garden, 1967 (Box 243, Folder 18)
        - -Interior, 1950-1960 (Box 243, Folder 19)
        - -Demolition, 1970 (Box 243, Folder 20)
  - -Fine Arts Center (post-1970) [FAC+]
    - -General, 1968- (Box 243, Folder 21)
    - -Asbestos Removal, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 22)
    - -Courtyard, 1978- (Box 243, Folder 23)
    - -Landscaping, 1970- (Box 243, Folder 24)
    - -Renovations
      - -Art Complex Program Ctte (ACPC) Report, 1968 (Box 243, Folder 25)
      - -Models, 1965-1970 (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - -Specifications, 1969 (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - -Specifications, 1998 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - -Photographs
      - -Exterior, 1972- (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - -Exterior-Construction, 1970-1972 (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - -Exterior-Courtyard, 1972 (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - -Interior
        - -General, 1973- (Box 244, Folder 7)
        - -18th-Century Collection Common Room, 1973; undated (Box 244, Folder 8)
        - -Art Study Room, 1973-1981 (Box 244, Folder 9)
        - -Gallery, 1972- (Box 244, Folder 10)
        - -Offices, 1973 (Box 244, Folder 11)
        - -Storage Facility, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 12)
        - -Studio and Classroom, 1972- (Box 244, Folder 13)
      - -Groups and Individuals, 1987- (Box 244, Folder 14)
    - Books: 2 volumes (Box 243.1)
  - -Flood in Hillyer, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 15)
  - -Gallery Assistants Program, 1980- (Box 244, Folder 16)
  - -Grants, 1976- (Box 244, Folder 17)
  - -Lectures, Gallery Talks, Special Programs, 1933- (Box 244, Folder 18)
    [see also Museum Seminar and see also Music and Film Events and see also Trips]
  - -Lectures, etca.-A Day Without Art, 1989- (Box 244, Folder 19)
  - -Lectures, etca.-Museum Disaster Workshop, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 20)
  - -Loans
    - -Abroad, 1929- (Box 244, Folder 21)
    - -Domestic, 1933 (Box 244, Folder 22)
    - -Rentals, 1932-1968 (Box 244, Folder 23)
    - -To Smith, 1935- (Box 244, Folder 24)
  - -Maintenance, 1965- (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - -Membership, 1948- (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - -Murals
    - -General, 1935- (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - -Egleson Fresco, 1939- (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - -Tamayo Fresco, 1943- (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - -Museum Seminar, 1986 (Box 245, Folder 5a)
  - -Music and Film Events, 1958- (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - -Paintings
    - -General, 1879- (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - -Courbet-La Toilette de la Mariee, 1929-1968 (Box 245, Folder 8)
      [see also Paintings-Photographs-1800s]
    - -Courbet-La Toilette de la Mariee-Acquisition, 1924-1949 (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - -Portraits, 1935- (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - -Photographs (of the Paintings) (Box 245)
      - -Medieval / Renaissance (Box 245, Folder 11)
      - -18th-Century (Box 245, Folder 12)
      - -19th-Century (Box 245, Folder 13)
      - -20th-Century (Box 245, Folder 14)
  - -Print Room, 1951 (Box 245, Folder 15)
  - -Publications
    - -Brochures and Pamphlets, 1987- (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - -Bulletin, 1921-1939 (Box 245, Folder 17)
      [see also bound copies]
    - -Calendar, 1987-1995 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - -Journal, 1982-1986 (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - -Newsletter / Calendar, 1995- (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - -Usage Guides, 1979- (Box 245, Folder 21)
    - -Why the College Should Have its Gallery of Art, 1980 (Box 245, Folder 22)
  - -Purchase Exhibitions, 1962- (Box 245, Folder 23)
  - -Quilts-Photographs, undated (Box 245.1, Folder 1)
  - -Sculpture
    - -General, 1963- (Box 245.1, Folder 2)
    - -Rodin-The Walking Man, 1965-1966 (Box 245.1, Folder 3)
    - -Photographs (of the Sculptures)
      - -Greek, Roman, Egyptian (Box 245.1, Folder 4)
      - -Medieval / Renaissance (Box 245.1, Folder 5)
      - -18th-20th Centuries (Box 245.1, Folder 6)
  - -Trips, 1978- (Box 245.1, Folder 7)
- Museum of Art-Exhibits
  [see also Appendix B for item-level list of oversize exhibit posters]
  - -1902 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - -1912 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - -1913-1914 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - -1926-1927 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - -1927-1928 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - -1928-1929 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - -1928-1929-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - -1929-1930 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - -1929-1930-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - -1930-1931 (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - -1930-1931-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - -1931-1932 (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - -1931-1932-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - -1932-1933 (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - -1932-1933-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - -1933-1934 (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - -1933-1934-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - -1934-1935 (Box 246, Folder 18)
  - -1934-1935-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 19)
  - -1935-1936 (Box 246, Folder 20)
  - -1935-1936-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 21)
  - -1936-1937 (Box 246, Folder 22)
  - -1936-1937-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 23)
  - -1937-1938 (Box 246, Folder 24)
  - -1937-1938-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 25)
  - -1938-1939 (Box 246, Folder 26)
  - -1938-1939-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 27)
  - -1939-1940 (Box 246, Folder 28)
  - -1939-1940-Clippings (Box 246, Folder 29)
  - -1940-1941 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - -1940-1941-Clippings (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - -1941-1942 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - -1942-1943 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - -1944-1945 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - -1945-1946 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - -1946-1947 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - -1947-1948 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - -1948-1949 (Box 247)
    - -General (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - -Pompeiana
      - -General (Box 247, Folder 10)
      - -Artifacts
      - -Clippings (Box 247, Folder 11)
      - -Programs and Invitations (Box 247, Folder 12)
      - -Speakers (Box 247, Folder 13)
      - -Photographs (Box 247, Folder 14)
  - -1949-1950 (Box 247, Folder 15)
  - -1949-1950-Clippings (Box 247, Folder 16)
  - -1950-1951 (Box 247, Folder 17)
  - -1950-1951-Clippings (Box 247, Folder 18)
  - -1950-1951-Correspondence-Winslow Homer Exhibit (Box 247, Folder 19)
  - -1951-1952 (Box 247, Folder 20)
  - -1951-1952-Clippings (Box 247, Folder 21)
  - -1952-1953 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - -1952-1953-Clippings (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - -1953-1954 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - -1953-1954-Clippings (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - -1954-1955 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - -1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - -1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - -1957-1958 (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - -1958-1959 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - -1958-1959-Piranesi Exhibit (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - -1959-1960 (Box 248, Folder 11)
  - -1960-1961 (Box 248, Folder 12)
  - -1960-1961-Shaker Studies (Box 248, Folder 13)
  - -1961-1962 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - -1961-1962-Fall (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - -1961-1962-Spring (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - -1962-1963 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - -1962-1963-Clippings (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - -1963-1964 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - -1963-1964-Clippings (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - -1964-1965 (Box 249, Folder 8)
  - -1964-1965-Clippings (Box 249, Folder 9)
  - -1965-1966 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - -1965-1966-Clippings (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - -1966-1967 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - -1966-1967-Clippings (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - -1967-1968 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - -1967-1968-Clippings (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - -1968-1969 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - -1968-1969-Clippings (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - -1969-1970 (Box 250, Folder 9)
  - -1969-1970-Clippings (Box 250, Folder 10)
  - -1970-1971 (Box 250, Folder 11)
  - -1971-1972 (Box 250, Folder 12)
  - -1972-1973 (Box 250, Folder 13)
  - -1973-1974 (Box 250, Folder 14)
  - -1973-1974-Clippings (Box 250, Folder 15)
  - -1974-1975 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - -1974-1975-Clippings (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - -1975-1976 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - -1975-1976-Clippings (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - -1976-1977 (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - -1976-1977-Clippings (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - -1977-1978 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - -1977-1978-Antiquity in the Renaissance (Box 251, Folder 8)
  - -1977-1978-Clippings (Box 251, Folder 9)
  - -1978-1979 (Box 251, Folder 10)
  - -1978-1979-Clippings (Box 251, Folder 11)
  - -1979-1980 (Box 251, Folder 12)
  - -1979-1980-Clippings (Box 251, Folder 13)
  - -1980-1981 (Box 251.1, Folder 1)
  - -1980-1981-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 2)
  - -1981-1982 (Box 251.1, Folder 3)
  - -1981-1982-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 4)
  - -1982-1983 (Box 251.1, Folder 5)
  - -1982-1983-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 6)
  - -1983-1984 (Box 251.1, Folder 7)
  - -1983-1984-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 8)
  - -1984-1985 (Box 251.1, Folder 9)
  - -1984-1985-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 10)
  - -1985-1986 (Box 251.1, Folder 11)
  - -1985-1986-Clippings (Box 251.1, Folder 12)
  - -1986-1987 (Box 251.1, Folder 13)